HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm 6199/007 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Financial Records Files on Microfilm
1966-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/007 mf
17.11 cubic feet
152 microfilm reels
Microfilm.
8254432
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), was a United States labor union representing workers of the hospitality industry, formed in 1891. In 2004, HERE merged with the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE) to form UNITE HERE. HERE and later UNITE HERE were affiliated with the AFL-CIO until September 2005, when the General Executive Board of UNITE HERE voted in to leave the AFL-CIO and join with the Change to Win Coalition.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organizaiton)
8254432
- Local #1 thru Local #6 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  roll #99/Master
- Local #6 thru Local #10 (Reel 2)
  reel 100/Master
- Local #11 thru Local #17 (Reel 3)
  reel 101/Master
- Local #17 thru Local #24 (Reel 4)
  reel 102/Master
- Local #24 thru Local #27 (Reel 5)
  reel 103/Master
- Local #28 thru Local #50 (Reel 6)
  reel 104/Master
- Local #40 thru Local #62 (Reel 7)
  reel 105/Master
- Local #64 thru Local #99 (Reel 8)
  reel 106/Master
- Local #100 thru Local #146 (Reel 9)
  reel 107/Master
- Local #150 thru Local #261 (Reel 10)
  reel 108/Master
- Local #264 thru Local #400 (Reel 11)
  reel 109/Master
- Local #414 thru Local #471 (Reel 12)
  reel 110/Master
- Local #479 thru Local #662 (Reel 13)
  reel 111/Master
- Local #681 thru Local 878 (Reel 14)
  reel 112/Master
- Local #879 thru Local #815-S (Reel 15)
  reel 113/Master
- Loc. 1, 89-90 thru Loc. 2, 1990, 1989-1990 (Reel 16)
  reel 114/Master
- Loc. 3, 89-90 thru Loc. 5, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 17)
  reel 115/Master
- Loc. 6, 1989 thru Loc. 6, 1990, 1989-1990 (Reel 18)
  reel 116/Master
- Loc. 6, 1990 thru Loc. 10, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 19)
  reel 117/Master
- Loc.10, 89-90 thru Loc. 11, 1990 (Reel 20)
  reel 118/Master
- Loc. 12, 89-90 thru Loc. 17, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 21)
  reel 119/Master
- Loc. 17, 89-90 thru Loc. 21S, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 22)
  reel 120/Master
- Loc. 24, 89-90 thru Loc. 24, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 23)
  reel 121/Master
- Loc. 24, 89-90 thru Loc. 25, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 24)
  reel 122/Master
- Loc. 24, 89-90 thru Loc. 26, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 25)
  reel 123/Master
- Loc. 26, 89-90 thru Loc. 30, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 26)
  reel 124/Master
- Loc. 30, 89-90 thru Loc. 42S, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 27)
  reel 125/Master
- Loc. 43, 89-90 thru Loc. 54, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 28)
  reel 126/Master
- Loc. 54, 89-90 thru Loc. 54, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 29)
  reel 127/Master
- Loc. 54, 89-90 thru Loc. 69, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 30)
  reel 128/Master
- Loc. 70, 89-90 thru Loc.84, 1989, 1989-1990 (Reel 31)
  reel 129/Master
- Loc. 84, 89-90 thru Loc. 99, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 32)
  reel 130/Master
- Loc. 100, 89-90 thru Loc. 100, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 33)
  reel 131/Master
- Loc. 100, 89-90 thru Loc. 126, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 34)
  reel 132/Master
- Loc. 126, 89-90 thru Loc. 215, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 35)
  reel 133/Master
- Loc. 217, 89-90 thru Loc. 225, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 36)
  reel 134/Master
- Loc. 226, 1990 thru Loc. 261, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 37)
  reel 135/Master
- Loc. 264, 89-90 thru Loc. 315, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 38)
  reel 136/Master
- Loc. 332, 89-90 thru Loc. 361, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 39)
  reel 137/Master
- Loc. 369, 89-90 thru Loc. 450, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 40)
  reel 138/Master
- Loc. 451, 87-88 thru Loc. 483, 1990, 1987-1990 (Reel 41)
  reel 139/Master
- Loc. 495, 89-90 thru Loc. 611, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 42)
  reel 140/Master
- Loc. 623, 89-90 thru Loc. 737, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 43)
  reel 141/Master
- Loc. 741, 89-90 thru Loc. 878, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 44)
  reel 142/Master
- Loc. 87, 89-90 thru Loc. 886, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 45)
  reel 143/Master
- Local #1 thru Local #5 (Reel 46)
  reel 144/Master
- Local #6 thru Local #11 (Reel 47)
  reel 145/Master
- Local #11 thru Local #16 (Reel 48)
  reel 146/Master
- Local #17 thru Local #24 (Reel 49)
  reel 147/Master
- Local #24 thru Local #29 (Reel 50)
  reel 148/Master
- Local #30 thru Local #50 (Reel 51)
  reel 149/Master
- Local #54 thru Local #74 (Reel 52)
  reel 150/Master
- Loc. #75 thru Loc. #88 (Reel 53)
  reel 151/Master
- Local #99 thru Local #155 (Reel 54)
  reel 152/Master
- Local #165 thru Local #272 (Reel 55)
  reel 153/Master
- Local #274 thru Local #442 (Reel 56)
  reel 154/Master
- Local #450 thru Local #636 (Reel 57)
  reel 155/Master
- Local #662 thru Local #886 (Reel 58)
  reel 156/Master
- Allgaier, Rhonda - Bergl, Leonard, 1981-1984 (Reel 59)
  reel 018/Master
- Blue, Steve - Cicardini, Joseph, 1981-1984 (Reel 60)
  reel 019/Master
- Clair, Joseph - Connolly, Val, 1981-1984 (Reel 61)
  reel 020/Master
- Contreras, Miguel - Fabian, Gail, 1981-1984 (Reel 62)
  reel 021/Master
- Farr, Florence - Fisher, Marilee, 1981-1984 (Reel 63)
  reel 022/Master
- Fitzgibbon, Thomas - Gamberg, Robert, 1981-1984 (Reel 64)
  reel 023/Master
- Gaspero, Samuel J. - Guthman, Gary, 1981-1984 (Reel 65)
  reel 024/Master
- Haller, Diane Bick - Hanson, Vernard H., 1982-1984 (Reel 66)
  reel 025/Master
- Hawthorne, John W. - Johnston, Linda, 1981-1984 (Reel 67)
  reel 026/Master
- Kamaras, Vangel - Kircher, William, 1981-1984 (Reel 68)
  reel 027/Master
- Klayman, Hyman B. - Koskoski, Jerry W., 1981-1984 (Reel 69)
  reel 028/Master
- Lavin, John P. - Lavin, John P., 1981-1984 (Reel 70)
  reel 029/Master
- Leavitt, Herman - Leefe, Donald, 1981-1984 (Reel 71)
  reel 030/Master
- Leopold, Gary F. - Luebbert, Francis, 1981-1984 (Reel 72)
  reel 031/Master
- Mc Castland, Paul P. - Madison, James, 1981-1984 (Reel 73)
  reel 032/Master
- Mahoney, Loretta - Meister, Paul, 1981-1984 (Reel 74)
  reel 033/Master
- Miller, Edward L. - Morris, Elizabeth A., 1981-1984 (Reel 75)
  reel 034/Master
- Morse, Harvey J. - O'Reilly, George, 1981-1984 (Reel 76)
  reel 035/Master
- Orton, Robert - Paulsen, Kenneth, 1981-1984 (Reel 77)
  reel 036/Master
- Perry, David S. - Rao, Robert, 1981-1984 (Reel 78)
  reel 037/Master
- Rees, Thomas - Rees, Thomas, 1981-1984 (Reel 79)
  reel 038/Master
- Rees, Thomas - Rees, Thomas, 1981-1984 (Reel 80)
  reel 039/Master
- Rees, Thomas - Richardson, D.B., 1981-1984 (Reel 81)
  reel 040/Master
- Richardson, Howard P. - Richardson, Howard P., 1981-1984 (Reel 82)
  reel 041/Master
- Richardson, Howard R. - Rodriguez, Emilio, 1981-1984 (Reel 83)
  reel 042/Master
- Richards, Paul - Savickas, Joann, 1981-1984 (Reel 84)
  reel 043/Master
- Schiffman, Herbert - Schiffman, Herbert, 1981-1984 (Reel 85)
  reel 044/Master
- Schiffman, Herbert - Siegel, David, 1981-1984 (Reel 86)
  reel 045/Master
- Sirabella, Vincent - Sirabella, Vincent, 1981-1984 (Reel 87)
  reel 046/Master
- Sirabella, Vincent - Sirabella, Vincent, 1981-1984 (Reel 88)
  reel 047/Master
- Smith, Richard A. - Stamos, James, 1981-1984 (Reel 89)
  reel 048/Master
- Stephenson, Arlene - Stormer, Dale, 1981-1984 (Reel 90)
  reel 049/Master
- Stormer, Dale - Stormer, Dale, 1981-1984 (Reel 91)
  reel 050/Master
- Stormer, Dale - Taylor, Donald, 1981-1984 (Reel 92)
  reel 051/Master
- Taylor, Steven E. - Unwin, Karen, 1981-1984 (Reel 93)
  reel 052/Master
- Vaccarino, Mario - Wilhelm, John W., 1981-1984 (Reel 94)
  reel 053/Master
- Zenich, F. - Miscellaneous, 1981-1984 (Reel 95)
  reel 054/Master
- Agriesti, Jo Marie - Dugan, John, 1985 (Reel 96)
  reel 055/Master
- Diaz, Ernesto - Flanagan, Seymour J., 1985 (Reel 97)
  reel 056/Master
- Galland, John - Herbekian, Roxie, 1985 (Reel 98)
  reel 057/Master
- Hilyer, Rhonda - Lee, Raymond, 1985 (Reel 99)
  reel 058/Master
- Levenson, Scott - Meister, Paul, 1985 (Reel 100)
  reel 059/Master
- Miller, Edward L. - Orton, Robert, 1985 (Reel 101)
  reel 060/Master
- Papageorge, George - Rees, Thomas, 1985 (Reel 102)
  reel 061/Master
- Reilly, Sara - Sanfilippo, Louis, 1985 (Reel 103)
  reel 062/Master
- Schiffman, Herbert - Stamos, James, 1985 (Reel 104)
  reel 063/Master
- Suffis, Joanne - Temmink, Bill, 1985 (Reel 105)
  reel 064/Master
- Tobin, James - Zelnich, Frank T., 1985 (Reel 106)
  reel 065/Master
- Agriesti, Jo Marie - Clancy, Kathleen M., 1986 (Reel 107)
  reel 066/Master
- Clifford, Paul - Fieldman, Bruce, 1986 (Reel 108)
  reel 067/Master
- Fisher, Marilee C. - Granfield, Bill M., 1986 (Reel 109)
  reel 068/Master
- Grogan, Bernard J. thru Kline, Kevin George, 1986 (Reel 110)
  reel 069/Master
- Koskoski, Jerry W. thru Leefe, Donald W., 1986 (Reel 111)
  reel 070/Master
- Luebbert, Francis thru Miller, Edward L., 1986 (Reel 112)
  reel 071/Master
- Miller, Mordecai F. thru Orton, Robert B., 1986 (Reel 113)
  reel 072/Master
- Papageorge, George thru Rao, Robert J., 1986 (Reel 114)
  reel 073/Master
- Rees, Thomas thru Richardson, Howard R., 1986 (Reel 115)
  reel 074/Master
- Richardson, Ronald thru Stamos, James, 1986 (Reel 116)
  reel 075/Master
- Stephenson, Arlene thru Weston, Deborah, 1986 (Reel 117)
  reel 076/Master
- Wilhelm, John W. thru Zenich, Frank T., 1986 (Reel 118)
  reel 077/Master
- International Audits Local #1, Western Reg. Office, 1973-1977 (Reel 119)
  reel 1/Master
- International Audits Local #1-Local #64, 1979-1987 (Reel 120)
  reel 2/Master
- International Audits Local #69-Local #166, 1979-1987 (Reel 121)
  reel 3/Master
- International Audits Local #166-Local #427, 1979-1987 (Reel 122)
  reel 4/Master
- International Audits Local #436-Local #737, 1979-1987 (Reel 123)
  reel 5/Master
- International Audits Local #737-IU Tip Fwd, 1979-1987 (Reel 124)
  reel 6/Master
- International Audits Local #1-Local #35 (Reel 125)
  reel 7/Master
- International Audits Local #40-Local #165 (Reel 126)
  reel 8/Master
- International Audits Local #166-Local #391 (Reel 127)
  reel 9/Master
- International Audits Local #400-Local #727 (Reel 128)
  reel 10/Master
- International Audits Local #737-Tip Fund (Reel 129)
  reel 11/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #1-Local #40, 1982-1983 (Reel 130)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #43-Local #215, 1982-1983 (Reel 131)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #217-Local #442, 1982-1983 (Reel 132)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #450-Local #741, 1980-1983 (Reel 133)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #746-Eastern Reg. Office, 1973-1984 (Reel 134)
- Quarterly Audits - Western Reg. Office, 1975-1983 (Reel 135)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #450-Local #727, 1984-1985 (Reel 136)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #737-Las Vegas J.E.B., 1984-1985 (Reel 137)
- Quarterly Audits - Audit Reports Loc. #1-Local #29 (Reel 138)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #30-Local #121 (Reel 139)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #122-Local #310 (Reel 140)
- Quarterly Audits - Local #312-Local #442 (Reel 141)
  reel 12/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #1-Local #83 (Reel 142)
  reel 13/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #84-Local #451 (Reel 143)
  reel 14/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #453-Western R. OFS. (Reel 144)
  reel 15/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #1-Local #21S (Reel 145)
  reel 16/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #23-Local #65 (Reel 146)
  reel 17/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #69-Local #206 (Reel 147)
  reel 18/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #215-Local #400 (Reel 148)
  reel 19/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #414-Local #623 (Reel 149)
  reel 20/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Local #628-CA State Council (Reel 150)
  reel 21/Master
- Quarterly Audits - Minn State Council - HERE Western Reg. Off. (Reel 151)
  reel 22/Master
- Locals - International Audits, 1979-1987 -- [reels 1-11], 1 (Reel 152)
- Quarterly Audits, 1981-1986 [reels 1-22], 2 (Reel 152)
- Expense Reports, 1966-1990 [reels 1-128], 3 (Reel 152)
- Local per capita tax reports, 1978-1996 [reels 1-225], 4 (Reel 152)